[Music]
if you look at the timing you know this
was just after the pandemic all of us
got you know locked down there was Panic
All Around
and after a couple of months of the
lockdown we started thinking that this
was probably a good time to think about
inorganic growth we started looking at
opportunities and and when you look at a
specific Target bharti AXA was really a
very uh apt Target for us in terms of
size it was roughly about 22 percent of
our size
it was doing well it was you know
scaling up
but it was still relatively subscale so
if you look at its business numbers we
measure our business and combine ratio
so combined ratio was a bit elevated but
if you split that roughly 78 percent was
lost and 42 percent was the expense
ratio in a total combined of 120 yeah
which basically showed you that the
business was underlying business was
fine it was just that it was upscale so
expenses were very elevated thirdly
there were certain uh distribution
Partnerships that they had which was
adding to our overall franchise and
lastly and to me this is very important
uh we like the the culture and the team
foreign
[Music]